Jose Chavez Digital Desginer

josechavez.design

in in/joseluischavez94

Bē /jlcdo894

jlcdominic94@gmail.com

San Diego, CA, 91913

(619) 897-5074

About Me

I'm a multidisciplinary designer, mainly focused on web design, who thrives in striking a balance between aesthetic and usability. My efficiency and easygoing personality makes me an effective designer. I also enjoy being a team player and solving problems. Throughout the years, I've been practicing and perfecting many different disciplines and areas of digital experience design such as UI/UX, web design, branding and identity, motion graphics, and video editing.

Education Background

Bachelor in Digital Graphic Design Engineering

CETYS University

Aug 2014 - Jul 2018

Skills & Proficiencies

- UI/UX Design
- Visual Design
- Branding & Identity
- Concepting & Ideation
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Graphic Design
- Frontend Development
- Video Editing
- Motion Graphics

- · Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Illustrator
- · Adobe After Effects
- · Adobe Premiere Pro
- · Adobe XD
- Google Analytics
- Wordpress
- Figma
- Sketch
- InVision

Professional Experience

Graphic Designer - AXIS

Aug 2016 - Jul 2018

- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.
- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.
- Offered design solutions that effectively solved problems and enhanced advertising goals.

Web Designer - Caliente Interactive

Aug 2018 - Feb 2021

- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug operations.
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Effetively multitasked and worked well with internal and external teams.

Courses & Certifications

- Adobe After Effects
 Udem,y 2017
- Adobe XD
 Udemy, 2020
- UI Design
 Udemy, 2020
- Sketch Intro Udemy, 2021

- Adobe Premiere Pro 4d Reality, 2017
- UX Design
 Udemy, 2020
- Web Dev. Bootcamp Udemy, 2020
- Figma Intro Udemy, 2021

Web Designer - AMASA

Feb 2021 - Present

- Fielded stakeholder questions and translated technical jargon into simplified concepts.
- Created and maintained a well-organized digital filing system and backups to reduce data loss.
- Enforced website standards for visual and design integrity.
- Coordinated workflows to optimize resources and prioritize high-volume workloads.